changex.com 2017-05-22

# Changex.com

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy explains the data processing practices of Changex.com.  

All Changex users (verified or not verified) shall grant us the right to collect, use and disclose their personal information in the manner described in the following Privacy Policy.

If you have any queries concerning your personal data or any requests in respect of these practices, please feel free to contact us via our email address support@changex.com.

## Data Protection

This Privacy Policy applies to all countries we work with. Personal information is collected when you provide personal data to the website Changex.com, for example when you register, verify your Changex.com account, use Changex.com services with or without authorization, submit a ticket or contact us via Live chat, skype or other programs.

 **We use your personal data to:**

  * establish  your identity for secure transaction,
  * improve the content of our website,
  * provide you with a more personalized service,
  * perform market research,
  * send you special offers and promotions via e-mail, telephone, SMS and post,
  * share aggregated information with third parties (such as our merchant partners) for both advertising and promotional purposes. We will not pass on your individual contact details unless you have given us specific permission to do so,
  * keep your data for security administration, legal and maintenance purposes.

To open Changex.com account for you, we need to get certain personal information, such as your real full name and e-mail. For verification we need you to provide a copy of your ID and any document with your name and current address such as a utility bill, bank statement or telephone bill.  

For certain optional transactions of your account we may also require financial information or personal documents such as bank account details.

For verification purposes Changex.com reserves the right to request proof of your identity and proof of address. When registering at Changex.com, your IP address is recorded in order to prevent fraud and increase security of our service.

Changex.com may as well collect additional information from you or about you in other ways not specifically herein. For example, we may request information related to your contact with our customer or support team.

We may store the results of your reply to a survey provided by Changex.com. We also reserve the right to collect the usage and access data that allows us to prevent multiple opening of multiple accounts or other fraudulent actions, which is performed for protection our system against illegal interference or abuse.

## Use of Personal Information

Changex.com shall use your personal information to operate your Changex.com personal account and render the services offered on the Changex.com website. We also share certain information with banks processing the services and identity verification services as part of our regular daily business operations.  

The purpose of sharing personal data is to identify and verify our customers, to limit fraudulent actions and other criminal activities. Moreover, it is necessary to manage our financial risk. By using the services of Changex.com (with or without completing a verification), you expressly consent to our collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with the procedure described in present Privacy Policy.

Changex.com will use the remarketing or similar audiences feature in AdWords. This feature is used for advertisement only. Third-party vendors, including Google, will show advertisement of Changex.com on their AdSense page. To be able to show ads based on the preferences of people, who visited Changex.com before, third-party vendors, including Google, will use cookies. Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Ads Preferences Manager.

## "Cookies"

Cookies information will be stored on your computer automatically. When you view the website Changex.com, there is a possibility we may store some data on your computer in the form of cookies to automatically recognize your PC next time you visit our website.  

Cookies can help us in many ways, for instance, they can be used to personalize our website with your interests or to store your password for a more convenient logging to your account.

## Customer Service Correspondence

When you send us correspondence, including emails, tickets and messages in Live Chat, we will store such information in our customer records. We shall also store your correspondence with the customer service and other correspondence with Changex.com.  

Changex.com administration retains these records in order to evaluate and improve our customer service, and to investigate potential fraud and any other violations. We communicate with customers via email to provide requested services or to resolve customer complaints.

Changex.com administration may use your email address to send you information about important changes in our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures required by the Terms and Conditions of Changex.com.
